<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Samer Costello - Costello // Unscripted</title><description>Thoughts, ideas and some terrible advice.
Written by @SamerCostello</description><link>http://samercostello.github.io/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 14:42:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://samercostello.github.io/author/samer/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>How 5 guys made $1000 in an hour on Playstation Network</title><description>&lt;h2 id="astoryofseizedopportunity"&gt;A story of seized opportunity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On December 6th 2014, in celebration of Sony's 20 years of Playstation, EA Chief Operating Officer Peter Moore took the stage at Sony’s PlayStation Experience event to reveal that Need for Speed: Most Wanted, Mirror’s Edge, and Plants Vs. Zombies: Garden Warfare are all free to download in the PlayStation Store for a limited time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.highdefdigest.com/uploads/jb/EA_201th_PS_free_games.jpg" alt="PS EA Offer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.digitaltrends.com/gaming/need-speed-mirrors-edge-plants-vs-zombies-free-playstation-right-now/#ixzz3LV5HF8Ga"&gt;Read more about the offer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a story of how 5 guys took advantage of that announcement, and made $1000 each from it a few days later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a warm Saturday afternoon, a couple of guys are lounging in the sitting room, enjoying a tournament of Fifa, when an unexpected phone call arrives. It's their friend Abat, notifying them of an offer about to end in a few hours. &lt;br&gt;
At first, they're not too interested, after all, some of them had no consoles of their own, and the others simply lacked the motivation to play such games. &lt;br&gt;
They were Fifa die hards through and through. &lt;br&gt;
But one of them saw and opportunity, and nothing, I mean, nothing motivates a human being like the smell of money(except maybe sex, and hunger...and a couple of other things. Ok so, maybe not nothing. But you get the point.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a matter of minutes, all 5 guys were on their laptops, setting up accounts. The process was rather simple:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Infiltrate the dealer, find the supplier. LOL :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.Setup Gmail account &lt;br&gt;
2.Use it to Sign Up for PSN &lt;br&gt;
3."Purchase" Games&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time the offer ended, they'd set up 103 accounts in total. These accounts were sold across several online platforms at $10 each. The accounts sold like hot cakes. I mean, who wouldn't wanna save $25 dollars on a game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three days later, all the accounts had been sold. The 5 guys met up to withdraw the money and split it amongst themselves. &lt;br&gt;
Their only regret was not having heard of the offer earlier. &lt;br&gt;
If $1000 dollars could be made in 2 hours, imagine how much they could have made in the 2 days the offer was running for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to lighten the mood a bit, here's a quote from Peter Drucker:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lesson learnt: &lt;strong&gt;Always be on the lookout for change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://samercostello.github.io/thousand-in-an-hour/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1f3bfe-1542-4126-99e8-e254dedd7e41</guid><category>musings</category><dc:creator>Samer Costello</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>